gscraper.com 2017-12-25

# Privacy GScraper - Fastest Scrape, Check, Filter, POST, Expand

We respect the privacy of our customers and users. This privacy policy is designed to help you understand what personal information we gather through your use of our website, software, and services and to help you understand what GScraper does with that information. Please read our privacy policy and our Terms of Use. In summary, our privacy policy lets you know that:

  * We may collect personal information from you when you use this website or our software. We will not use or disclose your personal information except for purposes set out in this privacy policy or as allowed by the People's Republic of China law.
  * We may use automated tools such as cookies to collect certain information about your visit to our website. Your browser may provide you with the ability to adjust settings relating to cookies.
  * We may gather more extensive information if we are concerned about abnormal website usage patterns or security breaches.
  * We can use your information to provide you with relevant information, allow others to provide you with information, and to communicate with you, and for other purposes set out in this privacy policy.
  * We may store your personal information, and do take several steps and precautions to protect the personal information that we store.
  * We will store credit card details in accordance with this privacy policy will delete credit card details upon request if we no longer require these details.
  * You should check the privacy policies of third party websites to which this website is linked, and we are not responsible for their conduct.
  * Please feel free to email our privacy officer should you wish to access or correct personal information we hold about you. We encourage you to update any outdated billing or contact information.
  * We may change this privacy policy from time to time, including to account for new services and technologies. We recommend that you should regularly check this privacy policy for changes or updates.

## Introduction

### About this privacy policy

GScraper values and respects the privacy of our customers and users. This privacy policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store personal information that you provide to us. www.gscraper.com (this 'website') is operated by GScraper. In this privacy policy, the terms 'we', 'us', and 'our' refer to GScraper.

By accessing and using this website, or using our software or services, you confirm your unconditional consent to our collecting, storing, using, and disclosing your personal information in the manner set out in this privacy policy.

### Terms of use

Please read this privacy policy in conjunction with our privacy policy in conjunction with our terms of use, which describes how you may use this website.

## How we collect personal information

### Collecting your personal information

We may collect personal information from you when you use this website or our software. We may also collect personal information that you provide to third-party websites or services, such as Facebook, Twitter, Clickbank, and Google Analytics. You may decide not to provide your personal information to us. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide you with access to certain information, services, or products.

### Automated collection

When you visit this website or use our software, we may use automated tools and methods (such as cookies, sessions, and usage monitoring software) to collect certain information about your visit or software use, including:

  * the internet protocol address and domain name used by your computer to connect to the Internet;
  * the operating system and the browser your computer uses, and any search engine or inbound hyperlink used to reach this website;
  * the nature of your use of our software or services, including information you input when using our software;
  * the date, time, and duration of your website visit;
  * and the pages viewed by you

This information will be used in aggregate form to analyse how this website or our software is being used, for example to analyse usage patterns in order to improve this website or our software. We will not disclose any such information except in aggregate form.

### Cookies

This website may use cookies and sessions to provide you with certain services or functionality. Cookies and sessions may be used to identify you as an individual user of this website. We use this technology to, amongst other things:

  * personalise your visits to this website;
  * eliminate the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information;
  * enable us to improve the content, reliability and functionality of this website;
  * evaluate the effectiveness of the advertising on this website; 
  * and track website usage patterns.

Using cookies will not give us access to any data on your computer other than the data stored in the cookie. Although you may configure your web browser to not accept cookies, you may experience a loss of functionality as a result.

### Collection of credit card details

We will collect credit card details where it is necessary for the following purposes:

  * to process the payment for which the credit card details were provided;
  * for a subscription that requires multiple payments over time;
  * or for your convenience (i.e., so that you can provide those details once instead of for every purchase).

### Additional collection

We may gather more extensive information if we are concerned, for example, about abnormal website usage patterns or security breaches.

## How we use and disclose personal information

### Use

We will not use or disclose your personal information except as provided in this privacy policy or otherwise in accordance with the Privacy Act 1993. We may use your personal information to:

  * provide you with services and information that you have requested;
  * assist our software to function;
  * help us debug or fix software problems;
  * provide you with support in using our software or services;
  * provide you with important notices and information about this website and our services;
  * provide you with other information (including promotional material, news, and event information) where you agree to receive such information;
  * verify your identity and to assist you if you forget your username or password;
  * improve or update this website and our products;
  * or enhance or improve the functionality of our software, including testing new or modified functionality;
  * respond to your enquiries and communicate with you;
  * and personalise this website in accordance with your preferences or enhance your user experience of this website or our software.

We may also combine data or information that we have retrieved from external sources or services with personal information that we hold, for any of the above purposes.

### Other use and disclosure

We will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to third parties. We may disclose your personal information to our professional advisors, contractors, service providers, business associates, related companies, and others who have agreed to treat your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. We may share your personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. We will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information except:

  * for any purpose set out in clause 8;
  * where you have otherwise authorised us to do so;
  * where we have given you notification of the intended use or disclosure and you have not objected to that use or disclosure in an anonymised form;
  * where we believe that such use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for national 
  * security in the performance of their functions;
  * where we believe that such use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce any legal rights we may have, or is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of us, our users, or others;
  * or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

### Deletion of credit card details

You may at any time request that any of your credit card details provided under clause 6 above be deleted. Please note that such deletion may cancel pending payments or subscriptions.

## Access to or correction of personal information

### Right to access and request correction

It is important to us that the personal information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date. If you are aware that this is not case and would like your personal information corrected, or simply desire access to your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer. You may request access to your personal information that we hold. Where you make any such request:

  * we may ask you to put your request in writing;
  * in some circumstances permitted by law, we may not provide such information to you;
  * where we decide not to correct or provide you with access to your personal information, we will give you our reasons for our decision;
  * where we provide the requested information or carry out the requested correction (or where we attach to that information a statement of any correction sought but not made), we may require you to pay a reasonable fee determined by us.

### Update information

To ensure that the contact and billing information we hold about you is accurate and current please advise us of all necessary changes to such information as soon as possible. 

## Other matters

### Third party websites

This website may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the content of such websites, or the manner in which those websites collect, store, use, and distribute any personal information you provide. When you visit third party websites from hyperlinks displayed on this website, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of those websites so that you can understand how the personal information you provide may be collected, stored, used and distributed.

### Changes to our privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by publishing the revised privacy policy on our website. Please check this privacy policy regularly for modifications and updates. If you continue to use this website or our software or services or if you provide any personal information after we make changes to this privacy policy, this constitutes your acceptance of those changes and the updated privacy policy.
